<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Buhooro Wellness, Retreat Wakiso, nr Entebbe, Uganda</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Buhooro Wellness, Retreat Wakiso, nr Entebbe, Uganda</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Buhooro Wellness Retreat, Wakiso, Uganda {year}.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 10:06:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stay</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/stay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 17:10:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/stay/</guid>
      <description>Your stay at Buhooro There are five staff permanently on site, with a guard taking care of security, and our excellent house keeper running the house and supervising guests. All our staff are friendly and welcoming.&#xA;The main part of the bungalow is open plan with kitchen-dining area and lounge combined, and the French windows look out over Lake Victoria. You can sit and take tea with the afternoon on-shore breeze cooling, either in the lounge or on the verandah.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/gallery/</guid>
      <description>The relaxing beauty of Buhooro Above: Fishermen head out on to the Lake.&#xA;Above: the beach with its naturally-occuring sand with a small rocky island just off the shore.&#xA;Above and below: The Verandah with spectacular views of Lake Victoria. Great for afternoon tea or taking lunch.&#xA;Above: The kitchen patio catches the evening sun.&#xA;Above and below: Many species of East Africans birds are frequent visitors including the iconic Crested Crane, a spectacular bird which is on the Ugandan flag.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 17:10:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/events/</guid>
      <description>The retreat is popular for many types of events, such as birthday and wedding parties, or any type of celebration.&#xA;And it&amp;rsquo;s perfect for photography, such as portraiture of weddings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Videography</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 17:10:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/video/</guid>
      <description>Our beautiful location is great for videography.&#xA;Below: video by Ugandan star Azawi. Shows exterior and interiors of the house and the tree swing over-looking the Lake.&#xA;Get in touch with us if you are interested in our location for your project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enquiry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/enquire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 17:10:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/enquire/</guid>
      <description> Title: Name (first name, last name): Your email address: Note: we will never share your email with anyone else. Give details of your enquiry; booking a stay, or event, or videography? Submit </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 10:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy We don&amp;rsquo;t put cookies in our pages to track visitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Success</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 12:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/success/</guid>
      <description> Your enquiry was sent successfully. Thank you. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 17:10:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/visit/</guid>
      <description>Make Buhooro your base camp to explore Uganda Both Entebbe and Kampala are a short drive from Buhooro. The Express Highway can take you all the way to Munyonyo and Ggaba in South Kampala.&#xA;Kampala has a buzzing nightlife and many bars and restaurants.&#xA;Entebbe has beautiful lakeside beach resorts and historic buildings as well as the Botanical Gardens which also hosts a very varied wildlife.&#xA;From Kampala, you can travel out of the capital to Jinja, and to Soroti in the north, as well as Mbarara and Kisoro in the westerly direction.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
